原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
我自己的节目
My own show.
你们正在收看的是本·洛克伍德的《锁定》
You are watching The Lockdown with Ben Lockwood.
爸爸  你出名了
Dad, you're famous.
在已知的二十多个外星世界里
Two dozen known alien worlds,
N金属是目前为止引入地球的
and Nth metal is just the strongest material
最坚硬的材料
brought to Earth from any one of them, by far.
自由代表夺走了我的一切
Agent Liberty took everything from me.
我要竭尽全力将他绳之于法
I will do anything to see him brought to justice.
谁是自由代表
Who is Agent Liberty?
你违背了许给菲奥纳的誓言
You betrayed your promise to Fiona.
你一旦越界  就回不了头了
Once you cross that line, there is no going back.
我有爱睡觉的病
I have that sleep thing.
-嗜睡症  -没错
- Narcolepsy? - Yes!
妈妈想给她找个医生
Mom was trying to find her a doctor,
但是尼娅说她已经有了
but Nia said she already had one.
她为什么要说谎呢
Why would she lie about that?
-天真热  -这还算好呢
- Hot day. - I've seen worse.
你在等人吗
Are you supposed to be meeting someone here?
我在等公交车
Waiting for the bus.
你睡起觉来真怪
You sleep weird.
你这个室友真不称职
Some roommate.
我说了不要让我睡着
I told you not to let me sleep.
我让你睡了两个小时
Uh, I gave you two hours
免得你在公司又一副萎靡的样子
so you wouldn't look like a crackhead at work again.
世界500强企业的老板
The average Fortune 500 CEO
每晚只睡五个小时
only gets five hours of sleep a night.
如果那些老板过劳死了
The average CEO doesn't get to be a CEO
就连老板都没的当了
if she's dead from exhaustion.
你需要一样跟曼彻斯特关系密切的东西是吧
You needed an object Manchester holds close, right?
能让我从精神上感应到他的东西就行
Anything that can help me reach him psychically,
衣服  珠宝
clothing, jewelry.
他在这里伤害过别人
He hurt someone in here.
他好像不管见到谁都会动手
Seems like he does that to everyone he meets.
出了这种事  我还是感到很抱歉
Man, I am still so sorry about what happened.
我把你引入了他的陷阱
I led you right into his trap.
你相信了他的善良  这有什么好道歉的
You're apologizing to me for believing the best in someone?
我一直相信人性本善
It's kind of my whole thing.
换做是你就不会让他逃脱
You wouldn't have let him get away.
但我让他耍了我
I did let him play me.
他怒气太盛  超出了你的控制  这很正常
Look, his... His rage was overpowering, you lost him. It happens.
但这件事情还没完
But it's not over yet.
这正是我所害怕的
That's what I'm afraid of.
我本以为曼彻斯特还有残存的善良
I thought there was some light left in Manchester,
但我审视了他的内心  善良已经荡然无存了
but when I looked into his mind, there was nothing left.
也许你能让他重拾善良
Maybe you can get it back.
指节铜环
Brass knuckles.
他倒有很强的民族自豪感
Well, he does have national pride.
这就行了
And Bob's your uncle.
超 女
第四季 第八集
别关门
Hold the door!
谢谢
Thank you.
你这是要为咖啡大战囤货吗
Stockpiling for the great coffee war?
不  我是给朋友带的
No, no. These are extras for friends.
等一下  抱歉
One more! Sorry.
-谢谢  -早上好
- Thanks. - Good morning.
詹姆斯
Hey, James!
尼娅  这全是你给自己买的吗
Hey, Nia. Are those all for you?
不  还有她帮朋友带的
No, she brought extra for friends.
怎么样了
So, how goes it?
莉娜在跟我保持距离
Lena is just being so distant.
我们会找机会聊聊  肯定有办法解决这个问题
I mean... We're gonna talk. I'm sure we'll work it out.
嗯
Yeah.
我是问文章怎么样了
I meant the article.
你还好吗
You okay?
-我没事  -尼娅
- Yeah, I'm fine. - Nia.
等等  尼娅  尼娅  等等
Wait. Nia, Nia. Wait.
我知道你最近不太正常
I... I know something's going on with you. I...
感恩节的时候  你提起自己的嗜睡症
At Thanksgiving, you told different people
跟每个人的说辞都不一样
different versions of your narcolepsy story,
根本都对不起来
and none of them matched.
现在你又狂灌咖啡
And now you're... You're drinking gallons of coffee
还被电视吓了一跳
and freaking out at the TV...
电视上的自由代表
Agent Liberty, on the TV,
让我想起了我做过的一个噩梦
it reminded me of a nightmare I had.
尼娅  我很担心你  也很想帮你
Nia, I'm getting worried, and I want to help you.
我真的没事
I'm really okay.
我就是自由代表
I'm Agent Liberty.
弗兰克
Frank...
说实话  你不是当领导的料
Respectfully, you are not leadership material.
不过我们知道你之前生活在雪莱岛上
However, we know you were on Shelley Island,
而且奇怪的是  你的身世被抹除了
and your background has oddly been erased.
所以我的直觉告诉我
So I've got a hunch
你能告诉我们自由代表是谁
you can tell us who Agent Liberty is.
我就是自由代表
I am Agent Liberty.
我们提出了认罪协议
We offer plea deals,
还告诉他们会把他们关起来
we tell them we're gonna lock them up,
但他们就一直重复同样的话
and they just keep saying the same thing.
这是斯巴达克斯的套路
Doing a Spartacus.
我是说  被抓的自由之子
By which I mean our captured Children of Liberty
声称自己就是英雄本人
claim the identity of their hero.
你开始补经典电影了
Oh, you're watching the classics?
烂熟于心
I'm mastering them.
你想聊聊导演主创论
Would you like to discuss auteur theory
-还有艾德·伍德的作品吗  -好啊
- and the works of Ed Wood? - Yeah, definitely.
凯特科那边有线索吗
Any leads from CatCo?
没有  但我们就快查到了
No. No, but we're getting close.
我的直觉[肠胃]已经能感受到了
I can feel it in my gut.
可能是益生菌的问题
Could be a probiotic issue.
但我同意
But I do concur.
自由代表的出现依然是个威胁
Agent Liberty's presence is still a threat,
即便  即便是没有...
even... Even without...
怎么了
What is it?
尼娅·纳尔今早看到这张照片后就慌了
Oh. Nia Nal saw that picture this morning and kinda freaked out.
-尼娅·纳尔  -是啊
- Nia Nal? - Yeah.
说是让她回忆起了噩梦什么的
She said it reminded her of a nightmare or something.
-谁知道是不是真的  -噩梦
- Who knows if that's true. - Nightmare?
而你就这样让她走了
And you just let her go?
-是啊  -你在说什么
- Yeah. - What are you talking about?
我没有办法告诉你我所知道的事情
There's no version of me telling you what I know
否则会影响时空连续性
that does not impact the space-time continuum.
等一下  等一下
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
在你们31世纪  尼娅·纳尔是谁
You know about Nia Nal in the 31st century?
什么  布莱尼  她是谁啊
What... Brainy, who is she?
我们最好不要讨论这事
Better we don't discuss that.
改变未来  蝴蝶效应
Future abrogation, the butterfly effect,
因果悖论  等等  等等
causal loops, etc, etc.
你觉得为什么我在感恩节的时候瞒着你
Why do you think I kept this from you at Thanksgiving
我已经简明地解释了她的重要性
when I so easily, yet expertly, deduced her import?
你所需要知道的
All you need to know
就是尼娅可能会带我们找到自由特工
is that Nia might be able to lead us to Agent Liberty.
-我们必须立刻去找她  -好好  但是...
- We must go to her at once. - Okay, okay. But--
她现在有些惊慌
She's a little freaked out right now,
所以或许让我来说这事吧
so maybe let me break the ice.
当然  没问题
Yes, of course.
好吧  行  去见尼娅吧
All right, fine. Just go see Nia.
有什么线索就通知我
Let me know if you have any leads.
然后  起码我有东西能报告给总统了
Then, at least, I'll have something to report to the President.
你是又要和总统去面对面了吗
Are you having another one-on-one with the President?
-我真希望哈雷被骂  -是啊
- Ooh, I hope Haley so gets yelled at. - Yeah.
这简直是个灾难
This is a complete disaster.
雪莱岛被拯救了
Lives were saved on Shelley Island,
很多本土恐怖分子伏法了
a dozen domestic terrorists were brought to justice.
我说的是我的民调数据
I'm talking about my poll numbers,
可是掉了一大截啊
which just got a big old shave!
不好意思  你是想依据民意调查来决定...
I'm sorry. You're letting polls dictate--
长官  我向你保证
Sir, you have my word.
只要我们搞掉这个组织的头领
As soon as we take down this organization's leader,
你的数据就会恢复以往的光辉
your numbers will be back to their usual luster.
如果你认为找到自由特工能解决这事
If you think finding Agent Liberty will fix this,
那就找到自由特工
find Agent Liberty.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
不  萨克  我是告诉你不要担心
No, Thack, I'm telling you not to worry.
《锁定》
本·洛克伍德
周二五点
我们发起的战争有多个战线
Look, the war that we are waging has multiple fronts.
支持我们的激进人士
Just because we've had setbacks on our more,
确实有些下滑...
uh, bellicose endeavors--
激进  就是"好战"  萨克
Bellicose. It means, "War-like," Thack.
好吧  萨克  听好
Okay, Thack, listen up.
自由特工吸引的是极端分子
Agent Liberty appealed to extremists,
而本·洛克伍德则是转化...
whereas Ben Lockwood is turning--
本·洛克伍德  我  我说的是我
Uh, Ben Lockwood, me. I mean, me.
我负责转化中立人士反抗超女和她的族类
I am turning the broader tide against Supergirl and her kind.
所以  我想要的只是...
And so, all I'm asking is...
我们能不能先别管自由特工
Can we-- Can we just put Agent Liberty aside for a little bit?
时机一到  他自会回归
He'll come back when the time is right.
与此同时
In the meantime...
现在  先让本来负责
Right now, let's... Let's let Ben drive.
他来了  本  你大学里的朋友来了
There he is. Ben, your friend is here from the university.
曼彻斯特·布莱克
Manchester Black.
我就是想来打声招呼
Thought I'd pop by and say hello.
曼彻斯特
Manchester...
你在哪里
Where are you?
所以我决定下午离开大城市
So, I decided to ditch the city for the afternoon
来看一看老友本杰明
and pay a visit to old Benjamin.
可以说是一石两鸟
Kill two birds with one stone, as it were.
我觉得你这样来
Well, I think it's very thoughtful of you
亲自感谢他非常体贴
to come all the way here in person to thank him.
他是这样  我也得这样
How could I not after what he did?
我说的是礼物  伙计
I'm talking about the gift, man.
礼物  对  没错  是礼物
The gift. Yes, of course, the gift.
什么礼物
What gift?
结婚礼物
The wedding gift.
送了一大套刀子给我和我未婚妻...
A great big set of knives for me and my fiancee...
菲欧娜
Fiona.
你还好吗  本杰明
You all right there, Benjamin?
曼彻斯特  告诉我你在哪里
Manchester! Tell me where you are.
我感受到你了
I feel you.
你还好吗
You all right?
是茶的问题吗
Is it the tea?
不是  茶很棒  谢谢
Nah, the tea's brilliant. Thanks.
然后  你看都喝完了
And, uh, well, look, all gone.
要不要我送你出去
Um, shall I walk you out?
好  我想可以
Yeah, I suppose so.
-很高兴见到你  -我也是  莉迪娅  谢谢
- It was lovely to meet you. - You, too, Lydia. Thank you.
茶很棒
Great cuppa.
好吧  你想找我  你成功了  放过她
Okay, you want me, you got me. Just... Just let her go.
但她可是贵宾啊
But she's the guest of honor.
现在  表现好点
Now, play nice.
走吧
Go on.
别轻举妄动
Easy, easy.
莉迪娅  能不能帮我们再泡点茶
Hey, Lydia, you mind grabbing some more tea?
曼彻斯特要在这多待一会
I think Manchester's gonna stay just a little bit longer.
好的
Oh. Yeah, sure.
继续说话  不然她会死得很惨
Say anything and she dies screaming.
-卡拉  -我知道你想一个人静静
- Kara. - I know you want to be left alone
等你听我说完  我一定会走
and I will absolutely do that after you hear me out,
因为我想我需要你帮忙
because I think I need your help.
你也需要我帮助
And I think you need mine.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的家人是来自
My family is from...
很遥远的地方
far away.
没关系
It's okay.
他们是来自一个叫纳尔托尔的星球
They're from a planet called Naltor.
那...
Wow, that's...
你可以告诉我的
You know you could have told me, right?
我知道现在不是
I mean, I know it's not the best time
告诉大家你是外星人的时机  但
to broadcast that you're an alien, but--
我了解我自己  非常了解
I know myself really, really well.
一直都很了解
Always have.
但是每一代
But once in a generation,
我们种族的一些女性会遗传解梦的能力
some of our women get this genetic oneiromancy.
她们可以梦见未来
They can dream the future.
你可以吗
And you can do that?
我的梦和你所想的不一样
My dreams aren't like you think.
我无法控制梦境
I can't control what I see.
大多数时候  我都不知道我的梦是怎么回事
Most of the time, I don't even know what's going on in my dreams,
但是当我知道的时候  太可怕了
and when I do, it's terrifying.
上次我梦到自由代表的时候
Last time I saw Agent Liberty
他们谋杀了一名女子
about to murder a woman.
你认识她吗
Did you recognize her?
你知道他什么时候  或是哪里下手吗
Do you know when he's going to do it or where?
这就是我想告诉你的
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
如果我能帮忙  我会的
If I could help, I would.
我真的会  但是我帮不了
Really, I would. But I can't.
如果我告诉你  我知道有人能帮你呢
Well, what if I told you that I know someone that could help you?
我很欢迎有人来帮我
I would welcome the help.
那就好
Great.
欢迎你来帮忙
Your help is welcomed.
-布莱尼  -美女
- Brainy? - Hey, girl.
我没事
I'm okay.
我想问问  你怎么会知道我这么多事
Can I ask you, how do you know so much about me?
-我是12级...  -他很聪明
- Well, I'm a 12th level-- - He's really smart.
你只要知道你所梦到的事
All you need to know is that what you see
不一定会成真
isn't necessarily what will be.
因此需要探究和解释
Hence, the need for exploration and interpretation.
所以我来了
But that is why I'm here.
你完全不必担心  努拉
So, you have nothing to worry about, Nura.
-你刚刚叫我努拉吗  -没有
- Did you just call me Nura? - No.
我没有  你叫她努拉了吗
I didn't. Did... Did you call her Nura?
她没有
She didn't.
那好
Now...
听着卡拉的声音倒数
Listen to Kara's voice and count backwards.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
-我进来了  -你看到了什么
- I'm here. - And what do you see?
一个吊钩
A hook.
起重机的吊钩
It's one of those loady type hooks.
上次我也梦到了
It was in the dream last time.
有看到什么新事物吗
Do you see anything new?
我不知道
I don't know.
-她要放松一点  -尼娅  没事  没事
- She needs to relax. - Nia, it's okay. It's okay.
放松一点  记住  这是你的梦境
Just relax, and remember, this is your dream.
她回来了
She's back.
那名女子
The woman...
她在震动
She's shaking.
太可怕了
It's awful.
我好像减慢了她的震动
I think I just slowed her down.
我可以让她不震动
I can stop the shaking.
她已经在调整梦境了
She's already modulating her dreaming.
那太好了  尼娅  太好了
That... that's great, Nia. That's great.
在这之后  我真的有一些后续问题要问
After this, I'm really gonna have some follow-up questions.
科林伍德
住手  放下枪  请你放下枪吧
Stop, put the gun down. Please, just put the gun down.
你吓到我了  求你把枪放下
You're scaring me. Please, put the gun down.
住手  我说了  请你住手
Stop! I said... Please, stop. Please, stop.
把枪放下
Put it down!
-这里还有其他人  -她得走近那个人
- There's somebody else here. - She needs to move toward it.
是自由之子的人
It's Liberty.
卡拉  我要出去
Kara, I want to get out.
正着数  一  二
Count forwards. One, two--
-我要立刻出去  -三
- I want to get out now! - Three.
我们在这  你很安全
Hey, we're here. You're safe.
但那名女子不安全
But that woman isn't.
我知道我们该去哪里了
And I know where we need to go.
科林伍德
高中州冠军
欢迎来到科林伍德
Welcome to Collinwood.
这里好像没这么差劲
It doesn't seem so bad.
没错  能出什么岔子呢
Oh, yes. What could go wrong?
洛克伍德寒舍参观到此就结束了
And this is the end of the Lockwood home five-cent tour.
莉迪娅  本杰明  你们有个温馨的家
Well, Lydia, Benjamin, you have a lovely home.
我还有一堆工作要赶着做
So, I've got tons of work I need to catch up on.
-我会...  -那是什么
- I would be-- - What's that?
那是本的曾曾曾祖父做的
Oh, Ben's great-great-great-grandfather made those.
对  他是个铁匠
Yeah. He was a blacksmith.
那把刺刀
That bayonet is the...
是洛克伍德家族钢厂的首批产品
Well, it's one of the first things the Lockwoods ever forged.
它参与过美国独立战争
It's from the American Revolution.
真的吗
Is it, really?
我能看看吗
Can I?
对...
So...
它曾经在邦克山古战场
You know, it's from Bunker Hill.
记得吗
Remember that one?
当时英国人以为他们赢了
It's the one where the Brits, uh, thought they had won,
结果战争太过血腥  以致于他们输了
but the battle ended up so bloody, that it cost them the war,
而牺牲毫不值得
and it wasn't worth it.
血腥才是对的
Bloody is right.
想象一下  把这刀插进人的身体
I mean, can you imagine sticking this into a bloke
并在五脏六腑搅动
and then twisting it in his guts?
-很有画面感  -画面感
- That's graphic. - Graphic.
没错
It is.
"洛克伍德"
"Lockwood."
很不错的作品
It's a fine piece.
你是否希望过丈夫是铁匠  莉迪娅
You ever wish your husband was a steel man, Lydia?
住手
Stop it.
当然  你们现在的事业跟铁匠无关了  对吧
Of course, that's not really the family business anymore, is it?
你们现在只是戴着邪恶的金属面具
Now you lot just dress up in wicked metal masks.
对不对
Isn't that right...
自由代表
Agent Liberty?
本  他在说什么
Ben, what is he talking about?
听我说  我这辈子从来没见过你
Okay. Listen, I've never seen you before in my life,
你口中的人不是我
and I'm not whoever it is that you say that I am.
曼彻斯特
Manchester.
曼彻斯特  告诉我你在哪里
Manchester, tell me where you are.
-滚出我的脑袋  -你承诺过
- Get out of my head. - You made a promise.
我的承诺和菲奥娜一起逝去了
That promise died with Fiona.
但在我这里没有逝去
But it didn't die with me.
如果你不能遵守承诺  我会遵守
If you can't hold yourself to that promise, I will.
什么
What?
我能感觉到你的痛苦  曼彻斯特
I feel your pain, Manchester.
放弃吧
Give this up.
你想感受我的痛苦吗
You want to feel my pain?
那就感受吧
Feel it.
你疯了  他不是自由代表
You're insane! He is not Agent Liberty!
你敢用生命保证吗  莉迪亚
Do you bet your life on that, Lydia?
在你们这栋完美的小家里
Somewhere in your perfect little house,
放着一套他实施恐怖行动的服装
there is a silly costume he puts on to go do terrorism.
把面具给我看看
Show me that mask.
在回忆中  很有可能不止一个人
In retrospect, it makes sense that more than one person
跑了科林伍德五千米赛跑
would have run the Collinwood 5K.
你能认出什么吗
Do you recognize anything?
不能
No.
我在梦里看到的
All I saw in my dream
只有那个女人  影子  还有吊钩
was the woman, the shadow, and the hook.
你觉得我们要找的会不会是
Do you think we should be looking for some
某个建筑工地
kind of construction site?
不  你看到的很可能只是标志
No. What you saw were probably symbols.
荣格  弗洛伊德
Jungian, Freudian.
在我们那里  称之为弗洛荣格
Where I'm from, we call them Frungian.
-抱歉  -不  尼娅  不必抱歉
- I'm sorry. - No. No, Nia. Don't be sorry.
我们走的是正轨  这样找是对的
We're on the right track. This is... This is good.
虽然我确实感觉到了当地人的敌意
Although I do sense some hostility from the locals.
意料之中
Not unexpected.
区域数据扫描结果显示科林伍德
My scan of regional data revealed Collinwood
曾经是反外星人活动的早期据点
as an early center for anti-alien activity.
确实感觉有点像《大清洗》
It does feel a little Purge-y.
2013年  詹姆斯·德莫纳克的片
James DeMonaco, 2013.
你不是只看经典片吗
I thought you were just watching the classics.
-然后呢  -我想跟你说点事  就一会
- And? - Let me talk to you for a sec. Just a minute.
当然
Oh, of course.
你先别看
Don't look now,
但是...
but these, uh,
那几个带着缉外星人犬的家伙
fine folks over here with the alien-sniffing dog,
-他们一直在跟踪我们  -谁  哪里
- they've been following us. - Who? Where?
-他们吗  -别看  回来  我说了...
- Them? - No! Stop it! Stop! I told...
我觉得他们是自由之子
I think they're Children of Liberty.
-你这是盲目猜测  -我用X光看了
- Presumptuous. - I X-ray'd them,
他们带着枪
and they've got guns,
女人的包里放了一张金属面具
and the woman has a metal mask in her purse.
-有问题了  -或许刚刚好
- Problematic. - Or it could be perfect.
我们与其在城里转来转去
Instead of wandering around the city
找尼娅梦里的女人
looking for the girl in Nia's dream,
不如直接去找
instead, why don't we
那个即将要袭击她的人
just find the guy who's going to attack her?
-自由代表  -没错
- Agent Liberty. - Yes.
他已经来了  或者马上就到
He's here, or he will be soon.
也许那三个人可以为我们指路
And maybe these three can lead us to him. Hmm?
兵不厌诈  很好
Chicanery! Very good.
我来引开尼娅  你负责处理那些新朋友
I'll distract Nia while you catfish our new friends.
回头找我  尼娅  一家手工艺品店
Hail me after. Look, Nia, a crafts store.
你知道腕带有什么魔力吗
Have you been introduced to the magic of lanyards?
你们好
Hello!
我想请你们帮我个忙
I was wondering if you guys could help me.
我做了"二三与我"测试  就是基因测试
I just did one of those 23andMe tests. That's, you know, the DNA?
我的真名是卡拉·利伯蒂[自由]
Anyway, my real name is Kara Liberty,
我是来找我的生父的
so I'm here searching for my birth dad.
代表
Agent.
-什么  -自由代表
- Excuse me? - Agent Liberty.
他就在附近  对吧
He's... He's around here somewhere, am I right?
这狗真可爱
What a cute dog.
他还挺...友好啊
He's, uh, friendly.
双钻挂带
Uh, double diamond lanyards.
这些挂带还真漂亮  尼娅
My, aren't these lanyards compelling? Nia?
这是来接我们的吗
Is this for us?
太快了吧
This is happening so fast.
他们在袭击卡拉
They're attacking Kara!
-尼娅  尼娅  -放开她
- Nia. Nia! - Let her go!
-尼娅  不要  -这个难对付了
- Nia, no! - This is problematic.
你真的不用这么做的  你只要...
You really don't have to do this, you can just...
-会没事的  -没事  我们被绑架了
- It's going to be all right. - All right? We've been kidnapped.
新闻报道第一课  被绑架就说明你找对路子了
Reporting 101. When you get kidnapped, you're on the right track.
但这话没道理啊
But that doesn't make any sense.
这话你得跟露易丝·莱恩说去
Tell that to Lois Lane.
-谁  -很简单
- Who? - It's simple.
我们等待时机
We bide our time,
然后突然行动  使出我们的超级...
and then spring into action using our super...
功夫
Kung fu.
功夫里有各种颜色的腰带
In which we have many belts in an aggressive rainbow of colors.
我们的计划进展顺利
Our plan is working.
看见了吗
Do you see this?
他们到处都有武器  设备
They have weapons everywhere. Equipment.
这是典型的坏蛋巢穴
This is textbook bad guy lair.
我们应该和他谈谈
We should talk to him.
你想告诉自由代表
Do you want to tell Agent Liberty
我们把记者带到他的俱乐部来了吗
we brought reporters to his clubhouse?
-尼娅  -刚才是谁打来的电话
- Nia? - Whose call was that?
他们都要死
They've got to die.
卡拉  布莱尼
Kara! Brainy!
有话跟他说吗
Got words for him?
他是杀人犯
He's a killer, you know.
嗯
Yeah.
杀害了我这潦倒的一生中最爱的人
Murdered the love of my whole, wasted life.
告诉我这不是真的
Please tell me this isn't true.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
都过去了  结束了  我打算停手了
It was done, it was finished. I was going to stop.
-穿上战服  -什么
- Put the suit on. - What?
我要你在做你所热爱的事时死去
I want you to die doing what you love.
-不  求求你  不要  -快点
- No, please, no. - Now!
真不可思议
That was amazing.
你刚刚那一招
That... That thing you did with
让子弹打在手铐上  你怎么做到的
the bullet and the cuffs, how did you do that?
我不知道  好像是条件反射
I don't know. It was like a reflex.
他开枪前我就预见了那一刻
I... I saw the moment before the gunshot.
我的能力从来没有过这样的发挥
The power's never worked like that before.
当时我就知道该怎么做了
I just knew what to do.
这也说得通  我们的能力就像肌肉
I guess that makes sense. Our powers are like muscles.
使用得越多  能力就越强
The more we use them, the stronger they get.
至少别人是这么告诉我的
Or so I've been told.
还有个问题  能提供线索的几个人都昏迷了
Just one problem, our only leads are still unconscious.
等等
Wait.
洛克伍德家族钢厂
上面写着"洛克伍德家族钢厂"
This says "Lockwood Family Steel."
-你觉得这个洛克伍德是... -本·洛克伍德
-You think Lockwood as in-- -Ben Lockwood?
给我电话
Phone, please.
本·洛克伍德的家族企业  洛克伍德家族钢厂
Ben Lockwood's family company, Lockwood Family Steel,
在外星环境改造不久后破产了
went bankrupt shortly after the terraforming events
这场灾难毁了这家工厂  杀死了本的父亲
which destroyed this factory and killed Ben's father.
我去找人帮忙
I'm gonna get help.
卡拉
Kara?
布莱尼  尼娅和我在科林伍德
Brainy, Nia and I are in Collinwood,
我们撞见了一帮自由之子
where we ran into a bunch of Children of Liberty.
你没事吧  你当然没事了
Are you okay? Of course you're okay.
他们带我们去了一家工厂  里面有武器和补给
They took us to this factory, and it has weapons and supplies,
像个作战室
war room stuff.
你猜这家工厂最早是谁的
But guess who the factory belonged to first?
本·洛克伍德
Ben Lockwood.
-什么  -你觉得他有可能
- What? - Do you think there is a chance
就是自由代表吗
he might be Agent Liberty?
那就看看他是不是
Well, let's find out.
弗兰克  认罪协议不用再考虑了
Hi, Frank. Uh, the plea deal's off the table.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
本来是为了让你合作  现在不需要了
It was for your cooperation, but now we don't need it.
我们知道洛克伍德就是自由代表
We know that Lockwood is Agent Liberty.
洛克伍德  谁
Lockwood? Who?
你还和他一伙  他还和他一伙
Oh, so, you're still siding with him. He's still siding with him.
你在和谁说话
Who are you talking to?
听着  你不说也没关系
Um, listen. You know what, that's fine.
但如果你改变主意了
But if you change your mind,
就从他们送你去的秘密据点给我打个电话
just give me a call from whatever black site they send you to.
等等
Wait.
是他
It's him.
-你确定吗  -我们找到了这个混蛋
- Are you sure? - We got the bastard.
不要
Stop!
快  起来
Come on, get up.
本
Ben.
穿好衣服准备迎接死亡了
All dressed up for his funeral.
等你死了
When this is over,
他们就只能用牙科记录来确认你的尸体了
they're going to need dental records to ID your body.
后退  后退
Stand back, stand back.
情况可能会更糟糕
It could be a lot worse.
像圣经里一样  一命换一命
We could go Biblical, eye for an eye.
你杀了菲奥纳  我就杀了她
You killed Fiona, I kill her.
感受到了吗
You feel that?
即将失去一切的痛苦感受
That's what it's like when you're about to lose everything.
你想怎么样  荣恩  你是无法说服我停手的
What do you want, J'onn? You're not going to talk me down.
我知道  对不起
I know. And I'm sorry.
-为什么道歉  -你让我别无选择
- For what? - You leave me no choice.
你说得没错  我不会停止复仇的
You're right. Because I'll never stop.
除非你杀了我
Not unless you kill me.
来吧  来吧  你可以做到的
Go on. Go on. I dare you. You know you can do it.
-不  -那你来这里干什么
- No. - Then why are you here?
快跑
Run!
你不该这么做
Shouldn't have done that.
洛克伍德
Lockwood?
-超女  -荣恩  怎么了
- Supergirl. - J'onn, what is it?
曼彻斯特在执行复仇计划
Manchester's on the warpath.
我不能确定  但我觉得他找到自由代表了
I couldn't see for certain, but I think he has Agent Liberty.
我会找到他们的
I'll find them.
我说了让你等卡拉来
I told you to wait for Kara.
好吧  我们一起走
Fine. We stick together.
我看见他们从这里过来
I saw them come through here.
-尼斯金属  - 是N金属
- Nith metal. - Nth metal.
世间最坚硬的金属
Strongest element in existence.
这里面就加了N金属
There's a bit of it in this.
我还以为这是一枚班级戒指
I thought that was a class ring.
我是在家受的教育
I was home-schooled.
等等
Well-- Wait.
就是这里
This is it.
这就是我梦里的地方
This is the place from my dreams.
我梦里的事情要发生了
It's all going to happen.
尼娅·纳尔
Nia Nal,
你蕴藏着伟大的潜能
you contain greatness.
我不能告诉你我是怎么知道的
I can't tell you how I know,
但是我们可以阻止这一切
but we can stop this.
你可以阻止这一切
You can stop this.
我可以阻止这一切
I can stop this.
你看到了更多的细节
You saw something, something... Something more.
布莱尼  我们需要撤出去
Brainy, we need to get back outside.
本杰明·洛克伍德  出来受死吧
Benjamin Lockwood! Come and get your medicine, lad.
我现在必须问问你
Now then, I suppose the requisite question is...
有什么遗言吗
Any last words?
我来这里是阻止他的  不要逼我也阻止你
I came here to stop him. Don't make me stop you.
你要开始告诉我暴力改变不了任何事情吗
Is this the part where you tell me violence won't change anything?
什么  什么
What... What...
-你对我做了什么  -这是卫星尘埃
- What did you do to me? - It's moondust.
锋利到能切割氪星人的基因
Sharp enough to cut Kryptonian DNA.
糟糕
Oh, nasty.
你刚刚吸入了一口卫星尘埃
You just got a lungful from one of the alien moons.
有些尘埃的直径仅为一纳米
Part of it is honed to a nanometer.
你体内肯定被割伤了
I bet you're just a bit softer on the inside.
如果你杀了他  你又是什么呢
If you kill him, what does that make you?
偏狭的左派
The intolerant left.
我们想赢下这场仗  就必须秉持道义
If we want to win this, we have to be better.
让我把他送进监狱  让人们看看他的真面目
Let me take him to prison, show people who he really is.
不要再愚钝了
Don't be daft!
那些人恨你
Those people hate you!
你可以穿上披风  说你是超级英雄
You can put a cape on, say you're a superhero,
但是对于他们这类人来说
but to him and everyone else like him,
你永远只会是个外星人
you'll only ever be an alien.
一只蟑螂
A roach!
该选择站边了  盲目乐观的姑娘
Time to pick a side, Pollyanna.
你要么和他们一边
You're with them,
做政府傀儡  无忧英雄
government stooge, Happy Meal hero,
要么跟我一边  把他们彻底铲除
or you're with me, and we string up the lot.
灭掉每个把社区变成战场的恐怖分子
Every terrorist turning your streets into war zones.
你一直说那是永无休止的斗争
You keep saying it's a never-ending battle.
不如我和你一起终结它
How about you and I end it together?
我永远不会像你一样
I'll never be like you.
是什么  你看见了什么
What is it? What do you see?
超女
Supergirl.
莉迪娅
Lydia!
-本  -亲爱的  你不能待在这里
- Ben! - Sweetheart, you can't be here.
我们必须...
We have to--
哎呦
Well, well.
不要
No!
铁钩[船长]
Hook.
斯皮尔伯格执导  1991年
Spielberg. 1991.
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
我没事  我没事
I'm all right, I'm okay.
我们要离开这里
We-- We've got to get out of here.
本
Ben?
本  本
Ben. Ben?
本  住手
Ben, stop!
本  不要
Ben, don't!
本  放下枪
Ben, put the gun down!
那是N金属  超女
That's Nth metal, Supergirl!
-别做无意义的挣扎  -我没在挣扎
- No point struggling. - I'm not struggling.
我在飞
I'm flying!
你是纳尔小姐吧
Miss Nal, right?
干得漂亮
Nice work.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你认为结束了吗
Think it's over?
我认为这是个开始
I think it's a start.
人们会看见他的真面目
Now people will see who he really is.
狭隘
Small.
他不是一场运动的引领者  他就是个屠夫
He's not a movement, he's a butcher.
而现在  他会为此付出代价
And now, he's gonna pay for it.
你们俩看见卡拉了吗
Have either of you seen Kara?
-见过啊  -我觉得她...
- Uh, yeah. - I think she--
-洛克伍德先生  有什么看法  -看法
- Mr. Lockwood, any comments? - Any comment --
我不知道  看看我的脸  瞧瞧他们干的好事
I don't know. Look at my face. Look what they did to me.
我之前戴面具是为了保护我自己和家人
Now, I wore that mask to protect me and my family
因为有些外星人不喜欢我的信仰
because there are aliens who don't like to hear what I believed
不愿意听见真相
don't like to hear the truth,
所以我现在露出了真面目
so I'm cards up.
那超女呢  你们知道我是谁  可她又是谁呢
What about Supergirl, huh? You know who I am. Who is she?
你来干什么
Why are you here?
两次你都放我走了
Both times you let me go on my merry.
这两次我都干了...
Both times I've gone on to do...
难以启齿的事情
Well, let's call it unspeakable things.
我认为  你打心底里是想让我逃走的
So my theory is part of you wanted me to get away.
你想让我做你做不到的事
Part of you wanted me to do what you couldn't.
你错了
You're wrong.
就因为你想当个该死的圣人
Ah, 'cause you want to be a bloody saint.
因为你不想再经历战争了  对吧
'Cause you ain't gonna study war no more, yeah?
你认为那是弱点吗
You think that's a weakness?
我觉得那是你的性格缺陷
I think it's a character defect.
几个星期前  你也有这样的缺陷
Couple of weeks ago, you had that same defect.
也许那就是我的诅咒
But maybe that's my curse,
相信不该相信的人
believing in people who don't deserve it.
你觉得我的灵魂还能被拯救吗  老兄
You think my soul's still up for grabs, old man?
是的
Yes, I do.
我认为你也有同感
And I think you do, too.
超女终于抓到他了
Supergirl really got him.
既然大家都知道洛克伍德是个戴面具的神经病
It's gonna be hard for Lockwood to come off reasonable
他就很难树立理性的形象了
now that everyone knows he's a psycho in a mask.
哈雷上校  丹弗斯局长
Colonel Haley, Director Danvers.
-你好啊  超女  -贝克总统
- Hello, Supergirl. - President Baker.
《人权活动家入狱》
"Human rights activist imprisoned."
是他们说的  不说我说的
Their words, not mine.
-人权  -是的  很多人
- "Human rights"? - Yeah, a lot of people,
很多资助者在问  一个为人民服务的政府
lot of donors are asking how can we tolerate this
怎么会容忍这种事发生
in a government that is supposed to be for the people.
难道外星人就不是了吗
That meant to imply that aliens aren't?
-不是什么  -人民  阁下
- Aren't what? - People, sir.
当然不是
Of course not.
但你也是个公务员  像我一样
But you are a government employee, like me.
所以  我们要确保
And, as such, we need to make sure
我们在为全国所有的人民服务
that we are serving all of the people of this country,
而不止是那些与我们意见相同的
not just the ones we agree with.
为了国家安全  从现在起
For reasons of national security, from now on,
超查部要求所有相关人员做到信息透明
the DEO will require full transparency from its assets.
我们要知道你的秘密身份  超女
We need to know your secret identity, Supergirl.
不行  我们不登记她的信息是有原因的
No. We keep her off the books for a reason.
-她不能告诉你  阁下  -为什么不能
- She can't tell you that, sir. - And why not?
洛克伍德刚刚指出了这点
Lockwood just shined a huge spotlight on the fact
你隐瞒了你的身份
that you are withholding who you really are.
保守这个秘密会让事情变得更糟
Now, keeping that secret inflames things.
让公众有更多理由不相信你和我的政府
Gives the public more reasons to distrust you and my government.
如果我说了  我认识的所有人
If I did that, sir, everyone I know,
我所爱之人都将处于危险之中
everyone I love would be at risk.
我的家人现在就在特勤处
My family is with the Secret Service as we speak.
你以为他们不身处危险之中吗
You think they're not in danger?
任何人都不应凌驾于我们其他人之上
No one should be above the rest of us.
我们要把国家放在首位
We need to put country first.
很抱歉  阁下  恕难从命
I'm sorry, sir. I can't give you what you want.
那我就只有感谢你的付出了
Then, I thank you for your service,
你被解雇了  立即生效
but you're dismissed, effective immediately.
希望你能服从
I hope you'll comply.
美国不想跟超女开战
The United States does not want a war with Supergirl.
那我相信你不会发动战争
Then I trust you won't start one.
给我点时间  他们会想通的
Okay, just give me some time. They'll come around.
保护超查部  以及它所代表的一切
Protect this place and everything it stands for.
谢谢  吉姆
Thanks, Jim.
我们正站在县监狱外面  本·洛克伍德
We are standing outside the county jail where Ben Lockwood
亦称自由代表  被收监于此
aka Agent Liberty, has been remanded into custody.
他们在抗议什么
What are they protesting?
抗议者在监狱外停留了
Protesters have been massing outside the jail
-长达几个小时  -我们
- for the last several hours... - Us.
已经阻断了交通
...and have blocked off roads...
纳欣诺市
男子中央监狱
自由
Liberty.
自由  自由  自由
Liberty. Liberty. Liberty.
-自由  自由  自由  -一会儿见
-Liberty. Liberty. Liberty. -See you soon.
自由  自由  自由
Liberty. Liberty. Liberty.
地球九十
你失败了
You failed.
你为什么要这样做
Why are you doing this?
这是你自作自受
You did this to yourself.
而今天  所有人都将毁灭
And now, all of you will perish.